challenge.com 2019-12-15

# Prüvit Privacy Policy

Pruvit Ventures, Inc. (“Pruvit”, “we” or “us”) respects the privacy of our users (“User” or “You”). This Privacy Policy explains how Pruvit collects, uses, and discloses, and safeguards Your Information when you visit the Pruvit website [www.pruvitnow.com](https://pruvitnow.com/) including any other media form, media channel, mobile website or mobile application related or connected thereto (collectively “Site” or “Sites”). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS THIS SITE.

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We will alert you about any changes by updating the “Revised” date of this Privacy Policy. Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting the updated Privacy Policy on the Site, and you waive the right to receive specific notice of each such change or modification. You are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates. You will be deemed to have been made aware of will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted the changes in any revised Privacy Policy by your continued used of the Site after the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted.

###### **Collection of Your Information**

We may collect information about you in a variety of ways. The information we collect on the Site includes:

Personally identifiable information, such as your name, shipping address, email address, and telephone number, demographic information such as date of birth, gender, location at time of use, and other information that you voluntarily give to use when you register with the Site or when you choose to participate in various activities related to the Site, such as online chat and message boards. You are under no obligation to provide us with personal information of any kind; however, your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain Site features.

Information our servers automatically collect when you access the Site, such as your IP address, your location at the time of access, your browser type, your operating system, your access times, and the page you have review directly before and after accessing the Site.

Financial Information, such as data related to your payment method (i.e. valid credit card number, card brand, expiration date, billing zip code) that we may collect when you purchase, order, return, exchange or request information about our products or services from the Site. We store only very limited, if any, financial information we collect. Credit card data is tokenized and held by a certified third party. Otherwise, all financial information is stored by our payment processors.

This Site may by default access your Facebook basic account information, including your name, email, gender, birthday, current city, profile picture, URL, as well as other information that you choose to make public. We may also request access to other permissions related to your account, such as friends, check-ins, and likes. You may choose to grant or deny us access to each of these permissions. For more information about open authorization and Facebook permissions refer to the Facebook Permissions Reference Page.

Personal and other information you may provide when entering contests or giveaways and/or responding to surveys.

###### **Use of Your Information**

Having accurate information about you permits us to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. Specifically, we may use information collected about you via the Site to:

  * Assist law enforcement and respond to subpoenas
  * Compile anonymous statistical data and analysis for use internally or with third parties
  * Create and manage your account
  * Deliver targeted advertising, coupons, newsletters, and promotions, and other information regarding our website and mobile application to you
  * Email you regarding your account or order
  * Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, and other transactions related to the Site
  * Monitor and analyze usage and trends to improve your experience with the Site
  * Notify you of updates to the Site
  * Offer new products, services, and/or recommendations to you
  * Perform other business activities as needed
  * Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft, and protect against criminal activity
  * Process payment and refunds
  * Resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems
  * Respond to product and customer service requests
  * Send you a newsletter or announcement

###### Disclosure of Your Information

We may share information we have collected about you on certain situations. Your information may be disclosed as follows:

If we believe the release of information about you is necessary to respond to a legal process, to investigate or remedy potential violations of our policies, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others, we may share your information as permitted or required by any applicable law, rule, or regulation. This includes exchanging information with other entities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

We may share your information with third parties that perform services for us or on our behalf, including payment processing, data analysis, email deliver, hosting services, customer service, and marketing assistance.

We may share your information with advertisers and investors for the purposes of conducting general business analysis. We may also share your information with such third parties for marketing purposes, as permitted by law.

If we reorganize or sell all or a portion of our assets, undergo a merger, or are acquired by another entity, we may transfer your information to the successor entity. If we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, your information would be an asset transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that the transferee may decline to honor commitments we made in this Privacy Policy.

###### Tracking Technologies

We may use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels, and other technologies on the Site to help customize the Site and improve your experience. For more information on how to use cookies, please refer to our Cookie Policy.

We may also partner with selected third-party vendors, such as Google Analystics, to allow tracking technologies and remarketing services on the Site through the use of first party cooked and third-party cookies, to allow us to analyze and track users’ use of the Site, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. By accessing this Site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by these third-party vendors. You are encouraged to review their privacy policy and contact them with any questions. We do not transfer personal information to these third-party vendors. For more information about opting out of interest-based advertising visit optout.networkadvertising.org.

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do-Not-Track feature or setting you can activate to signal your desire for privacy and to not have your online browsing activity monitored and collected. If you set the Do-Not-Track signal on your browser, we will honors such signals.

The Site may contain links to third-party websites and applications of interest, including advertisements and external services, that are not affiliated with us. Once you have used these links to leave the Site, any information you provide to these third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of your information. Before visiting and providing information to any third-party websites, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices of the third-party responsible for that website. We are not responsible for the contact or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other sites, services or applications that may be linked from the Site.

We use administrative, technical and physical security measures to help protect your personal information. While we have taken reasonable steps to secure the personal information you provide us, please be aware that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. No method of data transmission can be guaranteed against interception and other types of misuse. Although we try to keep the information you trust us with secure, we cannot guarantee complete security of your information.

We do not knowingly solicit information from or market to children under the age of 13. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under the age of 13, please notify us.

###### Options Regarding Your Information

You may review or change the information in your account or terminate your account by emailing customer support. Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with investigations, and enforce our Terms of Use.

If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails or other communications from us you may opt-out by: (1) noting your preferences at the time you register your account with us, or (2) contacting our support department.

California Civil Section 1798.83, permits California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the name and addresses of all third parties for direct marketing purposes in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to our support department. Please be aware that although publicly facing data may be removed, the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from our systems.

If you are under 18 years old and reside in California, and have a registered account with this Site, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Site. To request removal of such data, please contact the support department.

###### For Questions
